designertoday.com 2004-02-12

# 

**Privacy Statement for TIEMdesign- The Graphic Design Magazine  
**   
TIEMdesign- The Internet EYE Graphic Design Magazine has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web site: TIEMdesign \- The Graphic Design Magazine (aka The Internet EYE)

**Information Automatically Logged  **  
We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our Web site. IP addresses are stored in the server log files to detect server problems and also to track any sort of illegal system intrusions. We do not use IP addresses for any other purpose.

**Cookies  **  
Our Site uses cookies to make sure you don't see the same ad repeatedly. These are ASP (Active Server Pages) session cookies and do not track you in any way beyond TIEMdesign domain and our server. We also use Webtrends cookies to determine which areas of the magazine are the most popular, and to find out what sites are referring readers to the magazine. We use this information for no other purpose. These cookies do not collect any personal information.

**Advertisers  **  
We maintain our own ad serving technology and advertisers have only limited access to these resources (page view and clicks). We do not collect any personal information for advertisers.

**Personal Information  **  
This Web site does not request any personal information or collect any information that personally identifies you or allows you to be personally contacted. 

We do however collect personal information from our monthly drawings and the drawing sponsor(s) do receive the information for their own purposes (if they have requested the information) after the drawing concludes. The only way the sponsor receives your information is if you fill out a monthly drawing form. If you do not participate in a drawing then there is no collection of personal data. This is the only portion of the website that collects any personal data, and it is only through you entering data in the monthly drawing form. By entering personal data in the monthly drawing form you are giving the Internet EYE permission to forward that personal information to the contest sponsor. The data is not used in any other way or given to any entity other than the drawing sponsor for that particular month.

We also maintain a weekly newsletter. The only information we store is your e-mail address. It is not given out, traded or sold to any 3rd party. We only maintain the e-mail address list so that we can send the newsletter each week. Rest assured no one else has access to this data.

**External Links  **  
This site contains links to other sites. TIEMdesign- The Graphic Design Magazine is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. 

**Public Forums  **  
This site makes chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information. 

**Security  **  
This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. We use explicit permissions on any stored information (ASP session logs, contest databases, etc.). We also incorporate proactive intrusion detection and tracing of attempted breaches of the system and server.

**Contacting the Web Site  **  
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can Contact us.
